GIUSEPPE DI PALMA

Hi everybody! I'm 26-years old geek from southern Italy(Napoli). I am a developer, cloud enthusiast and master student of computer science at the University of Salerno. I work together with some international independent music megazine (Le Rane, Meeting del mare) as web content manager. Moreover, in my free time I practice juggling, but for now still at a low level.



CONTACT

dipalmagiuseppe1@gmail.com

+39 *** *** **

giuseppedp.page

github.com/GiuseppeDiPalma

in linkedin.com/dplmgspp

SKILLS

Programming skill

Java **Python** C/C++ Bash SQL **Swift** HTML/CSS

LaTeX

Cloud **Amazon Aws OpenStack** Azure

Server management

Linux Windows **FreeBSD** Linux distro

Ubuntu

CentOS

Next goal

AWS Solutions Architect Associate

Software & Tools

Docker **Wordpress**

LANGUAGE

Italian (Mother tongue) **English** (Level B2)

WORK EXPERIENCE

m 01/2020 - Present

Cloud Admin, Developer(Part-time) Omnia Visio, Aversa (CE) Design and implementation of cloud infrastructure for disaster recovery.

Development of android application. Server and website maintenance.

1 04/2019 - 09/2019

Cloud administrator(Internship) System Management, Cdn, (NA)

Enterprise cloud management and administration (AWS, Azure).

Server configuration and management for external customers (Enel, MetroMilano).

1 04/2018 - 06/2018

University internship System Management, Cdn, (NA) OpenStack cloud deployment, management and maintenance.

Management and maintenance of linux servers.

2014 - Present

Freelance Anywhere

Website building and management.

EDUCATION

09/2019 - Present

Master degree, computer science • Università degli studi di Salerno, (SA)

Specialization in Cloud Computing Expected type achievement: 2021

1 09/2014 - 08/2018

Bachelor Sc. degree ♥ Università di Napoli "Parthenope". (NA) Thesis: Using genetic algorithms to study the dynamics of insect populations.

1 09/2017 - 07/2018

iOS Essential **♀** Università di Napoli "Parthenope", (NA)

Approach to the Apple methodology, with the goal of developing a smartphone application in swift.

1 06/2016-10/2016

Hardware Technician **♀** Ami Training, Brusciano(NA)

Practical course on repairing computers and computer networks of various complexity.

PROJECTS

Word Count: Developing a solution for the problem word count for parallel environment built in cluster on AWS cloud.

BMC benchmark Generator: Benchmarch generator for lock-free

data structures written in C and Python. All my projects are available on my github page.

PERSONAL DATA

In compliance with the Italian legislative Decree no. 196 dated 30/06/2003, I hereby authorize you to use and process my personal details contained in this document.